Shilpa V

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India



shil.v.86@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/shilpa-v-bb69b3269

Summary

Experienced professional with a demonstrated history of working in the various industries. Skilled in Customer Success Management,

Client management, Client on boarding, Client Retention, E Communications, Team management, Leadership, Data analytics,

Client Solutions, Client Services, Client Sucess, Solutions Consultant.

Experience



Global Lead - Customer Success

Vitrina A.I.

Mar 2023 - Present (4 months)

Customer Advocacy, Customer Relationship, Customer Retention, Upselling, Customer Renewal, SaaS, B2B, Account Management, Post Sales, CRM tools, Client Servicing, Hubspot.

Key Responsibilities:

- -Develop and implement customer advocacy strategies to boost satisfaction and loyalty.
- -Foster strong customer relationships through effective communication and proactive engagement.
- -Drive retention initiatives by analysing customer needs and identifying engagement opportunities.
- -Collaborate with sales teams to identify upselling opportunities and maximize revenue growth.
- -Lead customer renewal efforts through proactive engagement, issue resolution, and contract negotiations.
- -Possess deep understanding of SaaS and B2B industry trends, providing valuable insights to customers and internal teams.
- -Manage key accounts as primary point of contact, handling inquiries, requests, and escalations.
- -Utilize CRM tools like HubSpot, Pendo, and Google Analytics for tracking interactions, managing pipelines, and generating data-driven reports.
- -Provide exceptional client servicing, resolving issues promptly and maintaining high customer satisfaction.
- -Collaborate cross-functionally to align customer needs with company offerings and deliver exceptional experiences.



CSM

Haptik

Nov 2015 - Jul 2020 (4 years 9 months)

Working with complex, multi-divisional, multi-geographical stakeholders, Client onboarding, Project/ Account Management, Client Retention & Growth, Business Reviews, ROI, CSAT, NPS, Churn management, MRR, Monitoring Customer support tickets, Expansion revenue, Upgrading the accounts with emerging technologies, Mediate between clients and the organisation and also work with crossfunctional teams (e.g. Sales, Product, Marketing, Services) and provide aid in product design and product development.

3 Consultant

Tapzo

Sep 2013 - Oct 2015 (2 years 2 months)

CSAT/DSAT Analysis

Client Handling

Client Relationship Management

Analyst

ALTISOURCE BUSINESS SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED

Feb 2013 - Jun 2013 (5 months)

Handling US mortgage and financial Aspects

Team Lead (Partner Experience)

Desire Manpower Services

Feb 2008 - Dec 2012 (4 years 11 months)

- ~ Responsible for the growth and Development of the company.
- ~ Resolving partner issues by using all available tools and resources.
- ~Work closely with internal teams to troubleshoot and solve issues experienced by our partners.
- ~ Provide an amazing support experience to our public figures and media publishers across the platform.
- ~ Solicit, organize and contextualize product feedback from partners.
- ~ Manage ticket flow and communications across multiple teams.
- ~ Led a team of 18 to 20 people.

Payroll Officer UK

Tesco

Jun 2007 - Dec 2007 (7 months)

Retail Payrolll UK (Business Services)

Education

Stanford University Graduate School of Business

Diploma in Product Management

Jun 2023 - Jun 2024

Bishop Cottons Bangalore

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Accounting and Finance Jun 2005 - May 2007

Licenses & Certifications

Customer Success Manager: Fundamentals to your CSM career - Udemy

Skills

Webinar Management • Webinar • Web Conferencing • Interpersonal Skills • Product Road Mapping • Attention to Detail • Software as a Service (SaaS) • Communication • Customer Advocacy • Case Studies